This film shows various car models from past competitions.
This is the traditional four-wheel camera group.
It identifies tracks visually - fastest wins.
Balance bike group has just two wheels.
It requires self-balancing like a bicycle.
Wireless group charges capacitors remotely.
Competitors race to charge fastest and run longest.
Beacon group: cars find and deactivate signals.
They "extinguish" random light/sound beacons.
Smart vision cars recognize ground patterns.
They classify and grab items using AI.
Off-road group reaches 70km/h speeds.
(Footage captured by drone)
Next: more "intelligent" groups.
They use powerful processors.
They simulate real-world tasks.
Like logistics and indoor navigation.
Some feature AI capabilities.
This robot has multiple sensors.
It maps surroundings and avoids obstacles.
Then calculates optimal paths.
Now: highlights from national finals.
ZJUT team wins national awards yearly.
Ranking top among hundreds of teams.
Thanks for watching!